1) Wheelchair walker
2) Train
I'm going to take the train now!
I'm getting on the train now!
It's my first time!
Shall we put him in?
Yeah!
GO!
Wheelchair walker.
This is Shichirigahama.
It's my first time here.
I did it!
There's a place where the train is involved, too.
It's fresh.
It's amazing! It's my first time.
I'm in!
You're sure? This is it.
Oh, my God!
Landing!
Yeah!
Here it comes!
See you next time!
Yeah!
I don't know, we're not used to this.
Here it comes! Are they here?
Yeah!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great! I knew it. It's the beach. The wind's coming.
Ocean! The ocean!
First single!
This is the scene we did at Coal Love.
The smell, the ocean.
It feels good, that's what it is.
Clouds.
It sure is!
What's wrong with it?
The wind.
Let it clear up.
It was great earlier, wasn't it?
Shio's fashion today.
All black.
Ta-da!
It's true! And it's like a one-tone coordinate.
One tone! But isn't this cute?
It's so cute!
Today's Risa-chan's coordinate is
Ta-da!
She was going to the beach today.
I thought a shorter skirt would be better than a long one.
I thought a short skirt would be better than a long one.
And then...
Yay!
And, you know, a little bit cute.
Here I come!
Yeah!
The train...
The signal...
Oh no!
Enoshimashita!
That's great! That's the Enoshima!
Where are they showing it? I mean...
The Enoshima is over there.
Oh, my God! The Enoshima?
Isn't it amazing?
Is it important? Put the Enoshima away.
This is the Enoshima.
Wow!
I can't stop laughing.
It's the ocean!
Oh, no! The sky! The ocean!
The ocean!
Oh, no!
It's over!
It's windy! It's the ocean!
It's totally different!
Yeah!
It's bad!
I want some acai!
You have acai?
We have acai!There's an acai goal!
Great!
You ready?
That one?
That looks good!
Oh, my God, that's good! Looks good!
Yeah!
We've got to be on our guard here.
omo
dea
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, guys.
Buh-bye, buh-bye, buh-bye, buh-bye, buh-bye.
Wow, aren't you big? Oh, man.
It's hard.
Asahi.
Asahi, yes.
How is it? It's so good. It's so good.
Really? It's too good!
Wait, don't make me laugh.
I didn't make you laugh. I didn't make you laugh.
I'm not laughing. I'm not laughing. I'm trying.
Is it on? Yeah, it's on.
Is it good? Fluffy?
Looks fluffy.
Looks good.
Oh, the cream.
It's so good!
It's so rich.
I didn't get a chance to eat it, but...
It's delicious.
Hey.
Hey, sweetie.
Hey. - Laughing.
Fluffy
Yes, everyone.
LOL
My favorite outfit.
I seriously can't take a picture of you the other day.
Is that what's happening to me? It got greasy.
Laughs.
Wait, I cried.
How did you know?
You look white.
My vision is white.
But there's so much of it.
Wow, this is so routine. This is routine.
Every time Risa spills something, Sho tells me she spills it again.
I wonder why she spills. And she usually notices.
Oh, it fell out. It's more like she didn't notice.
I didn't notice anything. I wish you'd use this white one.
Worse... these aren't new clothes... but they always get dirty the day they're worn.
I know. I told her to get new ones.
I'm so shocked. What if it doesn't come off?
It didn't come off. It didn't come off... a lot.
It's just... it's oil.
Next time.
Why? You didn't see it? When I'm eating.
But sometimes I eat like this and I drop this whole thing.
At home.
At home?
Hold it like this.
Yeah.
Balgoth.
I'm sleepy.
I'm getting sleepy.
Good night.
You didn't close your eyes?
Why not?
Oh, my God! I'm showing too much of myself. It's getting a little hard.
Come on, let's get dirty.
It's dirty.
You're always asking who I am.
Always. - Yeah.
You need to take care of her.You need care, don't you?
Oh, that's right.
What? Seriously, you still need nursing care.
Well, then, I'd like to go home after taking care of you.
Okay, then.
Thank you for dinner.
I've had a lot of fun.
I'd like to go home now.
I'm leaving.
Are you sure you're ready to go?
Okay.